<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string-array
    name="zodiac">
    <item>Aries</item>
    <item>Taurus</item>
    <item>Gemini</item>
    <item>Cancer</item>
    <item>Leo</item>
    <item>Virgo</item>
    <item>Libra</item>
    <item>Scorpio</item>
    <item>Sagittarius</item>
    <item>Capricorn</item>
    <item>Aquarius</item>
    <item>Pisces</item>
  </string-array>

  <string-array
    name="zodiac_details">
    <item>Aries is the first astrological sign in the Zodiac, named for the
      constellation of Aries, called The Ram in Hellenistic tradition, after
      the
      golden ram that rescued Phrixos, taking him to the land of Colchis.
      Aries
      is ruled by the planet Mars. Being the first sign in the zodiac,
      Aries is
      associated with the astrological first house. In Western
      astrology, Aries
      is often considered a masculine, positive (extrovert)
      sign. It is also
      considered a fire sign, and is one of four cardinal
      signs.[2] Birthstone is
      the Aquamarine. Individuals born when the Sun was
      in this sign are called
      Arians or Ariens.[3] Under the tropical zodiac, the
      Sun enters Aries on the
      moment of vernal equinox by definition on March 20,
      leaving it on or about
      April 20. Under the sidereal zodiac, it is currently
      there roughly around
      April 15 and May 15. In western astrology, this sign
      is no longer aligned
      with the constellation as a result of the precession of the equinoxes.
    </item>
    <item>Taurus is the second astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating
      from
      the constellation of Taurus. In astrology, Taurus is considered a
      negative
      (introvert) sign.[2] It is also considered an earth sign and one
      of the
      four fixed signs. Taurus is ruled by the planet Venus (which also
      rules
      Libra). Being the second sign of the zodiac, Taurus has been
      associated
      with the astrological second house.
      Individuals born within the
      period when
      the Sun was in this sign are considered Taurus
      individuals.
      Under the
      tropical zodiac, the Sun is in Taurus roughly from
      April 20 to
      May 21. In
      sidereal astrology, this sign is no longer aligned
      with the
      constellation as
      a result of the precession of the equinoxes.
    </item>
    <item>Gemini is the third astrological sign in the Zodiac,
      originating from
      the constellation of Gemini. In astrology, Gemini is
      considered a
      masculine, positive (extrovert) sign. Perhaps the most
      dominant Geminian
      characteristic is versatility. It is also considered an
      air sign, and is
      one of four mutable signs.[4] Gemini has been closely
      associated with the
      planet Mercury and is considered to be ruled by it. A
      planet god known for
      its intelligence, awakening, cleverness, wiseness,
      high education, wise
      man, or sage.</item>
    <item>Cancer is the fourth astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating
      from
      the constellation of Cancer. In astrology, Cancer is considered a
      feminine, negative (introvert) sign. It is also considered a water sign
      and is one of four cardinal signs.[2] Cancer is ruled by the Moon. Being
      the fourth sign in the zodiac, Cancer has been associated with the
      astrological fourth house. Individuals born when the Sun was in this sign
      are considered Cancerian individuals. Under the tropical zodiac, the Sun
      enters Cancer on the moment of summer solstice by definition, or roughly
      on June 21, leaving it around July 22. In western astrology, this sign is
      no longer aligned with the constellation as a result of the precession of
      the equinoxes[citation needed], and thus according to the more accurate
      sidereal zodiac, the Sun enters Cancer from roughly July 16 until August
      15.</item>
    <item>Leo (♌) is the fifth astrological sign of the Zodiac, originating from
      the constellation of Leo. In astrology, Leo is considered to be a
      masculine, positive (extrovert) sign. It is also considered a fire sign
      and is one of four fixed signs[2] ruled by the Sun. Being the fifth sign
      of the zodiac, Leo has been associated with the astrological fifth house.
      Individuals born when the Sun is in this sign are considered Leo
      individuals. Under the tropical zodiac, Leo is occupied by the Sun from
      July 23 to August 22 Under the sidereal zodiac, it is currently there
      roughly from August 10 to September 15. Leos also have a second animal,
      which in fact is the Tiger. Leos are the dominant Zodiac sign, and are the
      strongest of the years.</item>
    <item>Virgo (♍) is the sixth astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating
      from the constellation of Virgo. In astrology, Virgo is considered a
      negative (introvert) sign. It is also an earth sign and one of four
      mutable signs. Virgo is traditionally ruled by the planet Mercury,
      although Ceres has been suggested as the ruler of Virgo by some modern
      astrologers. Being the sixth sign of the zodiac, Virgo has been associated
      with the astrological sixth house.</item>
    <item>Libra is the seventh astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating from
      the constellation of Libra. In astrology, Libra is considered a
      masculine,
      positive (extrovert) sign. It is also considered an air sign
      and is one of
      four cardinal signs.[2] Libra is ruled by the planet Venus
      (which also
      rules Taurus). Being the seventh sign of the zodiac, Libra has
      been
      associated with the astrological seventh house.</item>
    <item>Scorpio is the eighth astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating
      from the constellation of Scorpius. Scorpio is considered a feminine,
      negative (introverted) sign by most modern astrologers. It is also
      considered a water sign and one of the four fixed signs.[2] The
      dwarf-planet Pluto is the ruler of Scorpio. As the eighth sign in the
      zodiac, Scorpio is associated with the astrological eighth house. The
      lower arrow pointing up in the Scorpio symbol represents the venomous tail
      of the Scorpion or claw of wolf.</item>
    <item>Sagittarius is the ninth astrological sign in the Zodiac,
      originating
      from the constellation of Sagittarius. Sagittarius is
      considered a
      masculine, positive (extrovert) sign. It is also a fire
      sign and one of the
      four mutable signs.[2] Sagittarius is ruled by the
      planet Jupiter.
      Individuals born when the sun was in this sign are
      considered Sagittarius
      individuals. Under the sidereal zodiac, the sun
      enters Sagittarius on
      December 17 to January 20. Under the tropical
      zodiac, it is there roughly
      from Sagittarius on November 22 and exits on
      December 21.</item>
    <item>Capricorn is the tenth astrological sign in the Zodiac,
      originating
      from the constellation of Capricornus. In astrology, Capricorn
      is
      considered an introvert sign.[2] It is also considered an earth sign
      and
      one of the four cardinal signs. Capricorn is ruled by the planet
      Saturn.
      Being the tenth sign of the zodiac, Capricorn has been associated
      with the
      astrological tenth house. Individuals born when the Sun was in
      this sign
      are considered Capricorn individuals. Under the tropical zodiac,
      the Sun
      enters Capricorn by definition at the moment of winter solstice,
      or roughly
      at December 21, and leaves it around January 20. In western
      astrology, this
      sign is no longer aligned with the constellation as a
      result of the
      precession of the equinoxes.[citation needed] Under the
      sidereal zodiac, it
      is currently there roughly from January 15 to February
      15.</item>
    <item>Aquarius is the eleventh
      astrological sign in the Zodiac, originating
      from the constellation
      Aquarius. In astrology, Aquarius is considered a
      masculine, positive
      (extrovert) sign. It is also considered an air sign and
      is one of four
      fixed signs.[3] Aquarius has been traditionally ruled by the
      planet
      Saturn, and, since its discovery, Uranus has been considered a
      modern
      ruler of this sign. Being the eleventh sign of the zodiac, Aquarius
      is
      associated with the astrological eleventh house.</item>
    <item>Pisces is the twelfth astrological sign in the Zodiac, which
      started
      from the Pisces constellation.
      It is also considered a water sign and one
      of the four mutable signs. Pisces
      has been traditionally ruled by the
      planet Jupiter, but since its
      discovery, Neptune has been considered a
      modern ruler of this sign. Being
      the twelfth sign, Pisces is associated
      with the astrological twelfth
      house.</item>
  </string-array>

</resources>
